abof.com 2017-06-12

# Privacy policy

##### PRIVACY POLICY

_Capitalized terms used under this Privacy Policy and not defined herein shall have the same meaning as ascribed thereto under the Terms and Conditions of Use_

Abof through its Website/Mobile Application, is extremely proud of its commitment to protect your privacy. We value your trust in us. We have adopted the following Privacy Policy, which is applicable to all Personal Information that you provide to abof through the Website/Mobile Application, either directly or which we get from your use of our Services.

You acknowledge that you are disclosing Personal Information voluntarily. Prior to the completion of any registration process on the Website/Mobile Application or prior to availing of any Services offered if you wish not to disclose any Personal Information you may refrain from doing so; however if you don't provide the Personal Information that is requested it is possible that the registration process would be incomplete and/or you would not be able to avail of the Services.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Personal Information that you may provide to third parties, such as through other Linked Sites. Please be aware that if you choose to visit such third party sites, you should contact such third parties directly to determine their respective privacy policies because that third party's privacy policy, and not this Privacy Policy, will govern your activities and any personally identifiable information you disclose while visiting the third party site.

abof expressly reserves at its sole discretion the right to change this Privacy Policy periodically in the future without prior notice to the Users. User shall review our Privacy Policy available at the Website/Mobile Application regularly to be sure you are fully current with our practices and procedures in this area. Your continued use of the Website/Mobile Application will be subject to the then-current Privacy Policy.

The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the Website/Mobile Application:

###### Overview

We respect and are committed towards protecting your privacy. As part of the normal operation of the Website/Mobile Application, we collect and, in some cases, may disclose Personal Information about you. This Privacy Policy describes the Personal Information we collect about you and what may happen to that Personal Information.

By accepting this Privacy Policy and our Terms, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your Personal Information in the manner prescribed in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into the Terms and subject to the terms of the Terms, governs all use of the Website/Mobile Application.

In the course of registering for and availing various Services we provide from time to time through our Website/Mobile Application, we may collect your title, name, gender, email address, postal address, delivery address (if different), telephone number, mobile number, fax number, payment details, payment card details or bank account details, service usage, log information, IP Address, data collected through cookies and other personally identifiable information (collectively "Personal Information") through the Website/Mobile Application. We may seek additional information for new services that may be offered by us from time to time. If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Website/Mobile Application, we may collect such information into a file specific to you, and it shall also form a part of your Personal Information. Your Personal Information will not be posted in areas of the Website/Mobile Application viewable by the public or other users of the Website/Mobile Application.

###### Our Use of Your Personal Information

Our primary goal in collecting personally identifiable information is to provide you with a smooth, efficient and customized experience. The Personal Information is used for two general purposes: to process your order, and to provide you with the best possible services. This allows us to provide services and features that are most likely to meet your needs, and to customize the Website/Mobile Application and our Services to make your experience easier.

###### Our Disclosure of Your Personal Information

Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your Personal Information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be required to disclose your Personal Information to the government, law enforcement agencies, or third parties under certain circumstances; third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications; or users or authorized users may independently abuse or misuse your information that they collect from the Website/Mobile Application in violation of our Website's/Mobile Application's Privacy Policy and Terms of Use. Therefore, although we use industry standard information security practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your Personal Information will always remain private.

As a matter of policy, we do not sell or rent any Personally Information about you to any third party. However, the following describes some of the ways that your Personally Information may be disclosed. 

**Advertisers:** We may aggregate (gather data across all Users) Personal Information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for other marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to identify you personally.

**Other Corporate Entities:** We may sometimes share data with our affiliates, subsidiaries, joint ventures and third party service providers that provide us with services and/or provide you with services. We use third-party service providers to process purchases you make and to monitor our Users' interests. To the extent that these entities have access to your Personal Information, we will ask them to treat it at least as protectively as they treat personally identifiable information they obtain from their other users or members. Our affiliates, subsidiaries, and joint ventures will follow privacy practices no less protective of all users and members than our practices described in this document, to the extent allowed by applicable law. It is possible that abof, its subsidiaries, affiliates, joint ventures or any combination of such, could merge with or be acquired by another business entity. Should such a combination occur, you should expect that abof would share some or all of your Personal Information in order to continue to maintain and provide access to the Website/Mobile Application.

**Legal Requests:** abof co-operates with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws relating to matters, such as intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any Personal Information about you to law enforcement and other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe reasonably necessary or appropriate, in connection with any investigation.

###### DATA RETENTION POLICY

We will retain data for as long as you use the Mobile Application and it would continue for a reasonable time thereafter. Please note that some or all of the provided data may be required in order for the Mobile Application to function properly. If you wish to stop us from collecting any personal Information or other data, you may uninstall the Mobile Application.

###### Transfer of Personally Identifiable Information

The Personal Information that we collect from you may be transferred to and stored at locations that are outside the territory of India. It may also be processed by staff operating outside the territory of India, who work for or are engaged by abof.

Since the transmission of any information across the internet is not completely secure, we have implemented strong security measures and will do our best to protect your Personal Information. That being said, we cannot ensure 100% security and any transmission is at your own risk.

###### Changing Your Personally Identifiable Information

abof gives you the ability to edit your Personal Information and preferences at any time. You have the right to refuse any marketing email from us in the future. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. We will, however, retain in our files and databases Personal Information you have requested to remove in order to use it in some circumstances, such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, and enforce our Terms and Conditions of Use. Further, such prior Personal Information is never completely removed from our databases due to technical and legal constraints, including stored "back up" systems. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your Personal Information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests.

###### YOUR CONSENT

By using the Website/ Mobile Application and by providing your information, you consent to the collection and use of the information in accordance with this Policy, including your consent to share the information.

###### Cookies

Cookies are small and unique information identifiers that we send to your computer, mobile, tablet or other devices when you visit the Website. This enables us to recognize your profile and your device on future visits and provide to you customized features. These identifiers assist us in remembering your preferences and chosen items, hence, enhancing your Website browsing experience and trying to ensure that the ads and offers you see are personalized to your shopping behavior. The Website also uses technologies like Google Analytics which works on the data collected and stored through cookies and other identifiers for marketing and site optimization purposes.

The acceptance of cookies is not mandatory for visiting the Website. Nevertheless, we would like to point out that many of the Website's features and functionalities are only possible with the activation of cookies. The Help menu on the menu bar of most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie and how to disable cookies altogether. If you do leave cookies turned on, be sure to sign off when you finish using a shared computer.

###### Security

abof uses reasonable security measures to safeguard the confidentiality of your Personal Information, such as firewalls, Transport Layer Security (TLS), and other physical and electronic security measures. However, you agree and acknowledge that "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet.

###### Mobile Privacy

We may offer you the ability for you to connect with the Website or use our Mobile Application, Services, and tools using a mobile device, either through a mobile application or via a mobile optimized Website. The provisions of this Privacy Policy apply to all such mobile access and use of mobile devices. This Privacy Policy will be referenced by all such mobile applications or mobile optimized Websites.

###### Questions and Grievances

If you have any questions or grievances about our privacy practices, please feel free to contact us at: [Customer Service](https://abof.custhelp.com/)

###### GRIEVANCE OFFICER

In accordance withInformation Technology (Reasonable Security Practices and Procedures and sensitive personal data or information) Rules, 2011 the name and contact details of Grievance Officer are provided below:

**Name:** Dr. Pragnya Ram

**Address:** Aditya Birla Management Corporation Pvt. Ltd., Aditya Birla Centre, S. K. Ahire Marg, Worli, Mumbai 400030.

**Email Id:**[ pragnya.ram@adityabirla.com](mailto:pragnya.ram@adityabirla.com)

**Phone No:** +91-22-24995000

##### PRIVACY POLICY

_Capitalized terms used under this Privacy Policy and not defined herein shall have the same meaning as ascribed thereto under the Terms and Conditions of Use_

Abof through its Website/Mobile Application, is extremely proud of its commitment to protect your privacy. We value your trust in us. We have adopted the following Privacy Policy, which is applicable to all Personal Information that you provide to abof through the Website/Mobile Application, either directly or which we get from your use of our Services.

You acknowledge that you are disclosing Personal Information voluntarily. Prior to the completion of any registration process on the Website/Mobile Application or prior to availing of any Services offered if you wish not to disclose any Personal Information you may refrain from doing so; however if you don't provide the Personal Information that is requested it is possible that the registration process would be incomplete and/or you would not be able to avail of the Services.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Personal Information that you may provide to third parties, such as through other Linked Sites. Please be aware that if you choose to visit such third party sites, you should contact such third parties directly to determine their respective privacy policies because that third party's privacy policy, and not this Privacy Policy, will govern your activities and any personally identifiable information you disclose while visiting the third party site.

abof expressly reserves at its sole discretion the right to change this Privacy Policy periodically in the future without prior notice to the Users. User shall review our Privacy Policy available at the Website/Mobile Application regularly to be sure you are fully current with our practices and procedures in this area. Your continued use of the Website/Mobile Application will be subject to the then-current Privacy Policy.

The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the Website/Mobile Application:

###### Overview

We respect and are committed towards protecting your privacy. As part of the normal operation of the Website/Mobile Application, we collect and, in some cases, may disclose Personal Information about you. This Privacy Policy describes the Personal Information we collect about you and what may happen to that Personal Information.

By accepting this Privacy Policy and our Terms, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your Personal Information in the manner prescribed in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into the Terms and subject to the terms of the Terms, governs all use of the Website/Mobile Application.

In the course of registering for and availing various Services we provide from time to time through our Website/Mobile Application, we may collect your title, name, gender, email address, postal address, delivery address (if different), telephone number, mobile number, fax number, payment details, payment card details or bank account details, service usage, log information, IP Address, data collected through cookies and other personally identifiable information (collectively "Personal Information") through the Website/Mobile Application. We may seek additional information for new services that may be offered by us from time to time. If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Website/Mobile Application, we may collect such information into a file specific to you, and it shall also form a part of your Personal Information. Your Personal Information will not be posted in areas of the Website/Mobile Application viewable by the public or other users of the Website/Mobile Application.

###### Our Use of Your Personal Information

Our primary goal in collecting personally identifiable information is to provide you with a smooth, efficient and customized experience. The Personal Information is used for two general purposes: to process your order, and to provide you with the best possible services. This allows us to provide services and features that are most likely to meet your needs, and to customize the Website/Mobile Application and our Services to make your experience easier.

###### Our Disclosure of Your Personal Information

Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your Personal Information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be required to disclose your Personal Information to the government, law enforcement agencies, or third parties under certain circumstances; third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications; or users or authorized users may independently abuse or misuse your information that they collect from the Website/Mobile Application in violation of our Website's/Mobile Application's Privacy Policy and Terms of Use. Therefore, although we use industry standard information security practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your Personal Information will always remain private.

As a matter of policy, we do not sell or rent any Personally Information about you to any third party. However, the following describes some of the ways that your Personally Information may be disclosed. 

**Advertisers:** We may aggregate (gather data across all Users) Personal Information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for other marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to identify you personally.

**Other Corporate Entities:** We may sometimes share data with our affiliates, subsidiaries, joint ventures and third party service providers that provide us with services and/or provide you with services. We use third-party service providers to process purchases you make and to monitor our Users' interests. To the extent that these entities have access to your Personal Information, we will ask them to treat it at least as protectively as they treat personally identifiable information they obtain from their other users or members. Our affiliates, subsidiaries, and joint ventures will follow privacy practices no less protective of all users and members than our practices described in this document, to the extent allowed by applicable law. It is possible that abof, its subsidiaries, affiliates, joint ventures or any combination of such, could merge with or be acquired by another business entity. Should such a combination occur, you should expect that abof would share some or all of your Personal Information in order to continue to maintain and provide access to the Website/Mobile Application.

**Legal Requests:** abof co-operates with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws relating to matters, such as intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any Personal Information about you to law enforcement and other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe reasonably necessary or appropriate, in connection with any investigation.

###### DATA RETENTION POLICY

We will retain data for as long as you use the Mobile Application and it would continue for a reasonable time thereafter. Please note that some or all of the provided data may be required in order for the Mobile Application to function properly. If you wish to stop us from collecting any personal Information or other data, you may uninstall the Mobile Application.

###### Transfer of Personally Identifiable Information

The Personal Information that we collect from you may be transferred to and stored at locations that are outside the territory of India. It may also be processed by staff operating outside the territory of India, who work for or are engaged by abof.

Since the transmission of any information across the internet is not completely secure, we have implemented strong security measures and will do our best to protect your Personal Information. That being said, we cannot ensure 100% security and any transmission is at your own risk.

###### Changing Your Personally Identifiable Information

abof gives you the ability to edit your Personal Information and preferences at any time. You have the right to refuse any marketing email from us in the future. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. We will, however, retain in our files and databases Personal Information you have requested to remove in order to use it in some circumstances, such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, and enforce our Terms and Conditions of Use. Further, such prior Personal Information is never completely removed from our databases due to technical and legal constraints, including stored "back up" systems. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your Personal Information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests.

###### YOUR CONSENT

By using the Website/ Mobile Application and by providing your information, you consent to the collection and use of the information in accordance with this Policy, including your consent to share the information.

###### Cookies

Cookies are small and unique information identifiers that we send to your computer, mobile, tablet or other devices when you visit the Website. This enables us to recognize your profile and your device on future visits and provide to you customized features. These identifiers assist us in remembering your preferences and chosen items, hence, enhancing your Website browsing experience and trying to ensure that the ads and offers you see are personalized to your shopping behavior. The Website also uses technologies like Google Analytics which works on the data collected and stored through cookies and other identifiers for marketing and site optimization purposes.

The acceptance of cookies is not mandatory for visiting the Website. Nevertheless, we would like to point out that many of the Website's features and functionalities are only possible with the activation of cookies. The Help menu on the menu bar of most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie and how to disable cookies altogether. If you do leave cookies turned on, be sure to sign off when you finish using a shared computer.

###### Security

abof uses reasonable security measures to safeguard the confidentiality of your Personal Information, such as firewalls, Transport Layer Security (TLS), and other physical and electronic security measures. However, you agree and acknowledge that "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet.

###### Mobile Privacy

We may offer you the ability for you to connect with the Website or use our Mobile Application, Services, and tools using a mobile device, either through a mobile application or via a mobile optimized Website. The provisions of this Privacy Policy apply to all such mobile access and use of mobile devices. This Privacy Policy will be referenced by all such mobile applications or mobile optimized Websites.

###### Questions and Grievances

If you have any questions or grievances about our privacy practices, please feel free to contact us at: [Customer Service](https://abof.custhelp.com/)

###### GRIEVANCE OFFICER

In accordance withInformation Technology (Reasonable Security Practices and Procedures and sensitive personal data or information) Rules, 2011 the name and contact details of Grievance Officer are provided below:

**Name:** Dr. Pragnya Ram

**Address:** Aditya Birla Management Corporation Pvt. Ltd., Aditya Birla Centre, S. K. Ahire Marg, Worli, Mumbai 400030.

**Email Id:**[ pragnya.ram@adityabirla.com](mailto:pragnya.ram@adityabirla.com)

**Phone No:** +91-22-24995000
